<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Yu's Website</title>
		<description>Talk data to me.</description>
		<link>http://hitchpy.github.io</link>
		<atom:link href="http://hitchpy.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Experiences with data scientist interviews</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;I have been looking for jobs recently because I am about to graduate soon. 
At the beginning of Feburary, I have two interviews for the position of (junior) data scientist. Those are my first ever interviews. Although I didn&amp;#39;t get offer from either of them, it was a great experience. I would like to share some of the experiences here, and some thoughts about the process. Since there were non-disclosure agreement, I will not give out detail but only the general ideas. Hopefully someone might find this useful for their own future preparation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It all began in the Engineering and Science career fair here at UC Davis around mid-Jan(quite awhile back already!). There are many tech companies but not so many have opening for data scientist position. I handed out about a dozen resume and talked to the representatives about what I have done and why I am competent for the job. Natually, they are all very polite and just told me to go back and wait for notice. Workday.inc provided a short interview opportunites that afternoon, and finally I was invited to have an onsite interview. The second interview was from Engage3, a startup here in Davis, focus on retailing. They called me a few days after the career fair. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;general-process&quot;&gt;General process&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Engage3&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Called me, scheduled an hour informal interview with one of the senior member of the data scientist team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Talked with him in a coffee house, about what they are doing, what visions they have about their product, and what kinds of skills they would expect from their candidates. I had quite a nice conversation. Two days later they invited me for another two hour in-depth interview.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The two hour interview includes two components, one is technical with two of the team members, the other one is behavioral. More detail later.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Workday&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mature company focus on enterprise software, especially in human management and finantial management etc. Beautiful office in downtown SF. They are rapidly expanding their data science team, and they expect it will play an important role in their future company plan.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;During that short half hour on-campus interview, one of the senior member in the team interviewed me. It covered some basic statistical concepts, at the undergrad level, and one SQL question, one data manipulation question. Nothing special and quite standard. I didn&amp;#39;t ace it but I think I did ok. HR sent out an email for onsite a few days later.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;components-of-the-main-interview&quot;&gt;Components of the main interview&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The term data scientist is widely used only in recently years and the role is not very well defined. Every companies have their own expectations, some more research oriented, some more software engineering related, some more like consulting etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;engage3&quot;&gt;Engage3&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They were very straightforward and had clear idea about what their candidate should be able to do. They expect you know your conditional probability well(do it like a bayesian!), they also expect that you have strong hands on skill. I was given a piece of Python script to debug, since now I mostly use R for day to day analysis, it took me a while to spot the bug. No the usual kind of algorithm questions for software engineer position and that is nice. Fundamentally I think it is important that data scientist know those concepts but in it&amp;#39;s core, it is about analytics, the ability to explore data and yield insight from them. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the behavioral site, they focus more on your personality, whether you can endure hardship(you can imagine the importance of the trait for a startup company). In hindsight, I should be more well prepared for this interview. Review the stat/probability concepts, and brush up my Python skill since most people outside stat would be more comfortable with Python/Java. They told me they will make the final desision next week and I got the rejection right on time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;workday&quot;&gt;Workday&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Six round of interviews, the people there are all very talented. PhD from Physics/Stat/machine learning, experienced software engineers etc. And one of them is about basic stat concepts again! &lt;strong&gt;Condition distribution&lt;/strong&gt;, can&amp;#39;t stress that point more. Two of the them are coding style interviews. Need to write out the solution in a whiteboard, and yes, they would prefer you do it with Python/Java. The questions weren&amp;#39;t hard and I wrote out the solutions with Python with some hints. One of the interview is focued on machine learning algorithms, how they works, how to train them, their pros and cons. Need to know your toolbox well! And finally the head of the team talked with me for a moment, about what they are doing and their vision. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After that I also briefly interviewed with Cablevision and some other companies as well but don&amp;#39;t have any offer yet. More hands on experiences is needed! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next post I will talk about the Kaggle competition [BCI Challenge]{&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.kaggle.com/c/inria-bci-challenge&quot;&gt;http://www.kaggle.com/c/inria-bci-challenge&lt;/a&gt;}. Which me and several my classmates joined and finally got 79 out of 270 teams.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2015 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
				<link>http://hitchpy.github.io/2015/03/Experiences-with-data-scientist-interviews</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://hitchpy.github.io/2015/03/Experiences-with-data-scientist-interviews</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Topic Modeling with Latent Dirichlet Allocation(LDA)</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Once upon a time when I was an undergrad, whenever I heard people talk about MCMC or EM algorithms, I would be like: WOW, Those sounds really cool!  Now that I have Bayesian inference and MCMC under the belt, it is amazing how many things I can understand and do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a presentation for my MCMC course, which is more on the theory side. But we can do anything related to MCMC, theory, application etc. Naturally I went to Quora to find some inspiration. Then I came across this amazing field of Bayesian non-paramentric, which includes Dirichlet process, Gaussian process, LDA etc. Those basically are the latest and greatest hits right now and are widely using in machine learning field. So get down to business, find papers, lecture videos and start learning!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;LDA is a fairly simple model, it has some limitations like you need to specify the topics number beforehand. But many improvements have been proposed since David Biel etc originally proposed it in 2003. Nevertheless, still a brilliant algorithm. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would like to comb through the model specification and the modeling fitting sometime for later reference. But for now I will just post the presentation that I have. Professor Choi explained collaped Gibbs a little bit more for us, great experence! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://s3-us-west-1.amazonaws.com/yu.public/YuPei_stat280.pdf&quot;&gt;My presentation slides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2014 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
				<link>http://hitchpy.github.io/2014/12/Latent-Dirichlet-Allocation-Tryout</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://hitchpy.github.io/2014/12/Latent-Dirichlet-Allocation-Tryout</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>test of converting Rmarkdown with plots</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see &lt;a href=&quot;http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com&quot;&gt;http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you click the &lt;strong&gt;Knit&lt;/strong&gt; button a document will be generated that includes both content as well as the output of any embedded R code chunks within the document. You can embed an R code chunk like this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-r&quot; data-lang=&quot;r&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;kp&quot;&gt;summary&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;cars&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot; data-lang=&quot;text&quot;&gt;##      speed           dist    
##  Min.   : 4.0   Min.   :  2  
##  1st Qu.:12.0   1st Qu.: 26  
##  Median :15.0   Median : 36  
##  Mean   :15.4   Mean   : 43  
##  3rd Qu.:19.0   3rd Qu.: 56  
##  Max.   :25.0   Max.   :120
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can also embed plots, for example:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;figure/unnamed-chunk-2.png&quot; alt=&quot;plot of chunk unnamed-chunk-2&quot;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note that the &lt;code&gt;echo = FALSE&lt;/code&gt; parameter was added to the code chunk to prevent printing of the R code that generated the plot.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
				<link>http://hitchpy.github.io/2014/11/Test-rmarkdown</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://hitchpy.github.io/2014/11/Test-rmarkdown</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>First Post!</title>
				<description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s face it, we all need to communicate our ideas with others. I started this page hoping that some of my thoughts/codes can reach out to more people and I can get more feedback from others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be a data scientist, you need to know a bunch of stuffs. And it takes time to be good at something. So the focus of the things that I do will mostly be:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Data cleaning&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Application of Statistical/ Machine learning algorithms &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Details of algorithms/data structure implementations&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some visualizations/result communications&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since I am trained as a statistician, &lt;strong&gt;R&lt;/strong&gt; will be my primary language, but I speak &lt;strong&gt;Python&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;C++&lt;/strong&gt; as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
				<link>http://hitchpy.github.io/2014/09/First-post!</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://hitchpy.github.io/2014/09/First-post!</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
